Tabitha Oanda

tkoanda@bu.edu | Boston, MA 02215

https://github.com/tabithako • https://www.linkedin.com/in/tabithaoanda/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Enthusiastic undergraduate student in Computer Science degree program keen to develop technical skills through dynamic roles as a student researcher or intern. Hardworking and organized team player with an affinity for fast-paced and challenging environments.

WORK HISTORY

Hands Movement. Nairobi, Kenya Founder and Director | 04/2014 - 07/2018

- Designed and fundraised innovative education development programs that relied on modern technology in collaboration with local leaders and teachers to improve learning outcomes
- Lead a team of 20 volunteers to conduct e-learning math classes in 4 different primary schools in Nairobi
- Managed a team of 40 volunteers in delivering the objectives of a sponsored medical campaign and the distribution of 500 solar lamps within a slum community in collaboration with The Nairobi Hospital

Boston University College Of Engineering IT. Boston , MA Student Worker | 09/2019 - 10/2019

• Provided technical support to clients within the university

Boston University Department Of Computer Science. Boston, MA Student Researcher | 10/2019 - Current

- Applied Python expertise to write and analyse code required for transfer learning using PyTorch
- Tested, modified and validated the classifiers used in the original journal article.(https://arxiv.org/pdf/1909.00134.pdf)

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

As a scientist, I believe it is necessary to coherently share my findings and experiences with scholarly and lay audiences. I share varied perspectives from different scientists on my YouTube channel, interSTEM(https://www.youtube.com/c/interSTEM). I hope to empower my audience with the information needed to make decisions and inspire them to pursue research in their own unique way.

SKILLS

- Research
- Scientific Writing
- Object Oriented Programming in Java and Python
- Pytorch for transfer learning
- Javascript, HTML, CSS proficiency
- Videography
- Basic skills in Amazon Web Services

EDUCATION

Boston University Boston, MA Expected in 05/2022

Bachelor of Arts: Computer Science

 Coursework in data structures and Java

Wheaton College Massachusetts

Some College (No Degree)

- Freshman (2018-2019)
- Coursework in Calculus I, Calculus II and Python Programming
- Dean's List Fall 2018, Spring 2019